To Ajay
that ah friends Yogendra Verma your friend
that help court judge friends today very
special patience is not subscribed for the districts
and subscribe in details
and subscribe to my channel
and subscribe
agreement committee center related
ICC long for a real time you get the
biggest and subscribe
subscribe and subscribe so
here if you subscribe you
get it in the entire market which in war I make you
sleep with a handful of sky here
except for a long time it is available in the entire market at half pricing
if this promotion goes on that
talk about the bill if those children have taken ghee and
chalisa on someone then proximity effect
28 38 when rationalization of appointed then
subscribe there subscribe and
subscribe here there
is no condition to block the road
if you have taken 50 lucky Australia decision only then
subscribe to the joke when you will get it and
subscribe 10 lakh generally you will
get extra next knowledge or 1956 is the next
subscribe again because you must subscribe to this channel
because nowadays whatever the situation is there in
it cough cold fever or any
For any small or big trip, any question is
taken to the hospital,
for which Amazon has said to
download and appoint their appointment,
subscribe to the village, friends,
you can take the policy of any company and
subscribe, here in two years,
which in itself is
qualification and introduction, 25000 is going in this year
and friends, when the business is going, the
second thing is that you will get it from the father of Amazon,
whose I am and punch is that friend,
secondly, you will not get good quality anywhere
and we change the oil, olive oil
and people should subscribe to the channel for appointment,
talk to us, subscribe to the channel,
yoga is appointed in the video